[{"answer": "Well, Piers, number one, thank you for having me.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "So what do you think went wrong here?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, I felt a huge disappointment.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "What did you feel when you watched those images?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "Of course she should lead the life she wants to lead.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Or should she be allowed to lead the life she wants to lead?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "It means that public opinion had been driven I think by the saturation coverage on television and all of the commentary, so that most people were directed to believe -- and, you know, I'm sure you wouldn't deny the fact you were directing people to think this -- that this woman killed her child.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Tell me about the -- I also love the fact that even then you could tell that you had this kind of firebrand attitude.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Jealous?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, it's so complicated.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Was it as simple as that?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Oh, Piers, come on, you've been through this, I'm sure.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "When you get criticized, what do you think is the biggest misconception about you?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "How has it come to this?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think you need to remember, too, that she is, from time to time, what's called a blackout drunk.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "How did you feel when your wife said this to you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Well, I'll tell you a few things.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What do you hope to achieve by speaking publicly about this?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "I won't rule any of those things out right now.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Is this a short, sharp, shock treatment that you have implemented here?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I think that we have certain things that were instilled in us from my mother and my father as we grew up.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "What is it that you say that keeps you all going?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I would say I'm closest to Billy.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Now, who are you closest to, would you say?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I think that you have been caught in the -- like many other people, in this web, because I think it has always been a plan of his.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Do you think he's serious about this kind of stuff?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "Of course, at the end of the day.", "docId": "110722pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "It's all about you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 490}]